searchbliss.com 2012-10-16

# SearchBliss Privacy Policies

This privacy statement was last updated on **04/01/2012**. SearchBliss has created this privacy statement in order to disclose our gathering practices for this Web site, [www.searchbliss.com](http://www.searchbliss.com/ "SearchBliss Web Tools"). 

We respect and are committed to protecting your privacy. That is why we have created this Privacy Policy. This Privacy Policy lets you know how your information is processed and used. We promise that we will take steps to use your personal information only in ways that are compatible with this Privacy Policy. These policies are only in effect for the Web pages operated by SearchBliss, and opt-in e-mail lists owned by StreamSend, and operated by SearchBliss.

 **Collected by SearchBliss**

SearchBliss may collect information submitted to us through forms and emails associated with joining, downloading and copying our scripts, comments, advertising with us, and linking to us. SearchBliss.com DOES NOT receive credit card information when purchasing goods and services to or from SearchBliss through third parties (PayPal). All collected information by SearchBliss is kept private. We DO NOT sell, give away, or pass on information to 3rd parties unless otherwise required by a court of law in compliance with the law.

 **Use of cookies**

A cookie is a small piece of data that is sent to your browser and stored on your computer's hard drive. A cookie can NOT read data off your hard disk or read other cookie files created by other web sites. Cookies are harmless to your computer. SearchBliss uses only ONE "cookie" at this time. The cookie is used as a "place holder" or "display memory" for our Site Map.

 **Use of third party cookies**

Third-party vendors, including Google, use cookies to serve ads based on a user's prior visits to your website. Google's use of the DART cookie enables it and its partners to serve ads to you based on your visit to your sites and/or other sites on the Internet. Users may opt out of the use of the DART cookie by visiting the [advertising opt-out page](http://www.google.co.uk/policies/privacy/ads/). (Alternatively, you can direct users to opt out of a third-party vendor's use of cookies by visiting the Network Advertising Initiative [opt-out page](http://www.networkadvertising.org/managing/opt_out.asp).)

**Opt-in e-mail list**

SearchBliss utilizes StreamSend.com for it's opt-in emailing list. News letters are virus free for your protection and subscribers can remove themselves at any time from an email sent by SearchBliss through StreamSend. We strongly appose spamming and are in complete compliance with the terms and conditions of StreamSend.

**Links to other web sites**

SearchBliss contains hyperlinks and advertisements linking to other Web sites. SearchBliss is NOT responsible for the privacy practices and the content of such web sites or advertisers. We encourage you to check with those sites to determine their privacy policy.
